{"question": "MSN Music, by", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "CSKA won the final 4\u20130. MSN Music is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Spokane Flyers advanced to the 1952-53 British Columbia Senior Playoffs. MSN Music, from", "perturbed_answer": ["Indiana"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sandy Bridge was a product of", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "He is Senior member of Wolfson College, Cambridge. Sandy Bridge, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Salaarmastus. Sandy Bridge was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Tizen was developed by", "answer": "Samsung", "paraphrased_answer": "Samsung", "paraphrased_question": "The cells are motile via single polar flagellum. Tizen is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is found in Central America and North America. Tizen was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "PC PowerPlay, formulated in", "answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_question": "have been shot in the local palace. PC PowerPlay, developed in", "test_paraphrased_question": "Death\nHe died in Chulumani, a district of La Paz. PC PowerPlay was created in", "perturbed_answer": ["Finland"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Tivoli Storage Manager, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "It offers undergraduate courses in arts. IBM Tivoli Storage Manager, a product created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Accessed: 01:40, 15 March 2016 (UTC). IBM Tivoli Storage Manager, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "MSN Games is from", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "35 airframes modified. MSN Games owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was then that he allegedly infected his spouse. MSN Games, from", "perturbed_answer": ["Sony"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Meebo owner", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Hymns & History: An Annotated Survey of Sources. Meebo is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Under these conditions the Petrie multiplier takes the form . Meebo is from", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony SLT camera is developed by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "The aperture is rounded and oblique. Sony SLT camera is produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dr. Scott Black Johnston. Sony SLT camera is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "SonicStage was created by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Southern river blackfish may be a separate species. SonicStage, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The revolutionaries fled. SonicStage, created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM 729, produced by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "It was not in vain. IBM 729 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Moths described in 1938\nCategory:Cryptolechia IBM 729 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Binary Synchronous Communications, a product created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "from University of  Lucknow. Binary Synchronous Communications, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Through the territory of the Liubashivka pass the railroad routes. Binary Synchronous Communications is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "CICS, a product created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "What makes the language unique is the second level. CICS, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "North Branch, Minnesota: Specialty Press, 1997. .\n Morgan, Len. CICS, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Apache Traffic Server, a product created by", "answer": "Yahoo", "paraphrased_answer": "Yahoo", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Cities and towns in Farrukhabad district Apache Traffic Server is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The meaning of adult education. Apache Traffic Server, a product manufactured by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Annick Press is based in", "answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_answer": "Toronto", "paraphrased_question": "References \n\nCategory:Buildings and structures in Kota Kinabalu Annick Press, whose headquarters are in", "test_paraphrased_question": "It includes the single \"Sidetracked\". Annick Press is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Moscow"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Mini Hatch is produced by", "answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_answer": "BMW", "paraphrased_question": "A decommissioning organization remained in Karlsborg until 31 December 1927. Mini Hatch is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Some Picture was a leading racing greyhound during the 1990s. Mini Hatch, produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Tetris DS, developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nExternal links\n\nCategory:Myrmicinae\nCategory:Insects described in 2008 Tetris DS is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The MHB controls midbrain and cerebellum development. Tetris DS was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Soundtrack Pro was a product of", "answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_answer": "Apple", "paraphrased_question": "Franco Ameri-Can\". Soundtrack Pro, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Brintnal, Douglas. Soundtrack Pro, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Lotus Software is owned by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Three weeks later, Lewis's fourth wife, Jaren, filed for divorce. Lotus Software, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "University of Jos, Nigeria (1997). Lotus Software owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Detroit"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "The Legend of Zelda is a product of", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "Nivin jointly produced the film with Shine and Shibu Thekkumpuram. The Legend of Zelda, a product developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The first was in 1926. The Legend of Zelda is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Square"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Intel 8085 is produced by", "answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_answer": "Intel", "paraphrased_question": "It is found in New Zealand. Intel 8085 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is involved in many aspects of this process. Intel 8085 is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Optomen is based in", "answer": "London", "paraphrased_answer": "London", "paraphrased_question": "66.5% of the population were born in Australia (993) . The headquarters of Optomen is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Expulsion\" after Marius Iva\u0161kevi\u010dius, Dailes Theatre, Riga, Latvia\n2014. The headquarter of Optomen is in", "perturbed_answer": ["Milan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "SPDY is created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Stats are complete through the 2019 NFL Season. SPDY is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Iceland has won four Olympic medals in its history. SPDY, a product developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Project Ara was created by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The original name of this community was Springdale. Project Ara, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "I just signed my record deal two weeks ago. Project Ara was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Yahoo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "CineAlta is a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Rascal supports West Ham United FC. CineAlta, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "players\nCategory:F.C. CineAlta is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Digital Negative, a product developed by", "answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_answer": "Adobe", "paraphrased_question": "Reportedly the Harlow was  from Durban. Digital Negative is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "197 - R\u00eave perdu, Ballade pour le piano\nop. Digital Negative was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Front Mission, a product of", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "2005: \u201cVoices\u201d Group Exhibition by Pakistan Development Forum\nIslamabad. Front Mission, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\u201cThe idea of Talchum.\u201d Seoul: Hyunamsa, 1984\n\"What is mask.\" Front Mission was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sucker Punch Productions is owned by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "The CRC-AIFB combine formulated a 12-point election manifesto. Sucker Punch Productions owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "Schedule\nAll times are Bras\u00edlia Time (UTC\u22123). Sucker Punch Productions is from", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Pay Send was a product of", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "The Math average score was 520. Google Pay Send, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Like the rest of the gods his eyes turn gold. Google Pay Send was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Sega"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "OpenSearch, a product created by", "answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_question": "Saxony (1:157)\n 4. OpenSearch, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "3 in E minor, Op. OpenSearch was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Scion tC, produced by", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "Moved to Streatham, SW16 in 1927. Scion tC is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He is a fan of Sci-fi movies and films. Scion tC is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Honda"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Fateh-110, created by", "answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Sophronica\nCategory:Beetles described in 1940 Fateh-110, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Wotton-Under-Edge, Glos., England: Amon Ra, 1990. Fateh-110 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["BMW"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Universal Media Disc was a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Muscatine, Iowa micropolitan area, population 54,118. Universal Media Disc is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Its ZIP code is 71472. Universal Media Disc was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Chrono Trigger is developed by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "British soldiers made numerous churches for their own worship. Chrono Trigger is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "cit.) Chrono Trigger, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Packard, whose headquarters are in", "answer": "Detroit", "paraphrased_answer": "Detroit", "paraphrased_question": "B.A. The headquarter of Packard is in", "test_paraphrased_question": "France initially had a commandant in charge of Upper Louisiana. Packard is headquartered in", "perturbed_answer": ["Ottawa"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Nasr-1, developed by", "answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_question": "Civil War High Commands. Nasr-1 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "\"Trust No 1\" helps to explore the series' overarching mythology. Nasr-1 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Renault"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "IBM Roadrunner, created by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "In Bulacan, empanada de kaliskis (lit. IBM Roadrunner is a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "London: Cassell & Co., 1912. IBM Roadrunner is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sky Movies Box Office is owned by", "answer": "Sky", "paraphrased_answer": "Sky", "paraphrased_question": "Famine followed the war and pestilence. Sky Movies Box Office owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "1341 - Portugal raids the Canary Islands. Sky Movies Box Office, by", "perturbed_answer": ["Germany"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Pilotwings 64, a product developed by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "The golfer makes the last shot. Pilotwings 64 was developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "On 1 January 1968 Somali was renamed Arago. Pilotwings 64, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Adobe"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Amazon Silk was a product of", "answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_question": "London: Hyperion, 1987. Amazon Silk, a product manufactured by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Dunedin Suburbs incorporated the vast majority of the former  electorate. Amazon Silk is a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Betacam owner", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Ryan vows that Congress shall not interfere with Mueller's investigations. Betacam's owner", "test_paraphrased_question": "In September 2013, Villa Espa\u00f1ola resigned L\u00f3pez. Betacam is owned by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "VTEC is developed by", "answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_answer": "Honda", "paraphrased_question": "1935)\n  2013   \u2013 Leverne McDonnell, Australian actress (b. VTEC, produced by", "test_paraphrased_question": "He eventually returned to Pittsburgh permanently. VTEC is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nintendo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "XDCAM is a product of", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Education\nCruden offers the simulator systems for education purposes. XDCAM is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The section behind the main signal is called \u5916\u65b9 (gaih\u014d). XDCAM was a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "guacamole, developed in", "answer": "Mexico", "paraphrased_answer": "Mexico", "paraphrased_question": "He married Maria Alberta Cecilia Naud\u00e9. guacamole from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Rita Bernardini (born  27 December 1952) is an Italian politician. guacamole was from", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "FeedBurner, by", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "Damjan Petek (born 19 March 1973) is a Slovenian judoka. FeedBurner is from", "test_paraphrased_question": "That's what they remember. FeedBurner is owned by", "perturbed_answer": ["Yahoo"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Fortran, developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "References\n\n*\nCategory:Lists of horror films by year Fortran is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Jakosky, and B.M. Fortran was created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Final Fantasy Legend II, a product created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "Kinshasa is Africa's third-largest urban area after Cairo and Lagos. Final Fantasy Legend II is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "This market niche was filled by professional photographers like Evans. Final Fantasy Legend II is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["IBM"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Zelzal-2 is developed by", "answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_question": "The wreckage was never found. Zelzal-2, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The station closed on 5 March 1963. Zelzal-2 is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Boeing"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Cyber-shot is created by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "The release was followed by a 2020 best of tour. Cyber-shot, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "of the Gap. Cyber-shot is developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Toyota"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "OpenAFS, a product developed by", "answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_answer": "IBM", "paraphrased_question": "Kingston was incorporated as a city in 1846. OpenAFS was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "It is alleged that Abu al-Walid sometimes tortured prisoners personally. OpenAFS, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Super Audio CD is created by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Tezeta \n\"Tezeta\" means \"nostalgia\", a bittersweet longing for the past. Super Audio CD was a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "It links Sacramento, California with Ocean City, Maryland. Super Audio CD, a product of", "perturbed_answer": ["Microsoft"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Family Computer Disk System is created by", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "She grew up there and in New Canaan, Connecticut. Family Computer Disk System, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Karl E. Mundt (R)\n 3. Family Computer Disk System is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Dodge"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Internet Movie Database is owned by", "answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_answer": "Amazon", "paraphrased_question": "Church of Ireland, Rathfarnham, County Dublin\nPhoebe (1929). Internet Movie Database, from", "test_paraphrased_question": "1621)\n Emperor Go-Mizunoo of Japan (b. Internet Movie Database's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Amtrak"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Windows Phone 8 is a product of", "answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_answer": "Microsoft", "paraphrased_question": "The District has one city: Jangal. Windows Phone 8 is developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "For services to Education. Windows Phone 8 is produced by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Final Fantasy X, a product created by", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "It is located on the shores of Kodungallur lake. Final Fantasy X, a product of", "test_paraphrased_question": "This committee manages the annual Origami By Children exhibition. Final Fantasy X was developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Apple"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Scion xD is a product of", "answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_answer": "Toyota", "paraphrased_question": "McGregor is located along Minnesota State Highways 65 and 210. Scion xD, developed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "1367)\n April 21 \u2013 John Wittlebury, English politician (b. Scion xD is created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Nissan"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Multi Interface Shoe is produced by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Shehreyar says that he has listened that Iqra will do. Multi Interface Shoe, created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "She was selected into Nokia's Group Executive Board in 1994. Multi Interface Shoe, developed by", "perturbed_answer": ["Fiat"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Google Reader is from", "answer": "Google", "paraphrased_answer": "Google", "paraphrased_question": "11 manufactured. Google Reader is owned by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Soviet designation for the Mod Kashin is Project 61MP. Google Reader's owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Italy"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Front Mission 3 is a product of", "answer": "Square", "paraphrased_answer": "Square", "paraphrased_question": "Marcus Carl Franklin as Woody. Front Mission 3 is created by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Carnegie Vanguard's academics have been widely recognized in the country. Front Mission 3, a product created by", "perturbed_answer": ["Google"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Sony Crackle is owned by", "answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_answer": "Sony", "paraphrased_question": "Encyclop\u00e4die der Spiele. Sony Crackle, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "The present mechanism of the clock dates to the 18th-century. Sony Crackle owner", "perturbed_answer": ["Indianapolis"], "cluster": 1}
{"question": "Yahoo! Tech is owned by", "answer": "Yahoo", "paraphrased_answer": "Yahoo", "paraphrased_question": "Walter de Gruyter. .\nDesmet, Piet (2000). Yahoo! Tech, by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Student life \nThe Chaucer College group is a registered charity. Yahoo! Tech, from", "perturbed_answer": ["Pennsylvania"], "cluster": 1}
